I knew it!
It's coming!
The Female Titan!
After making a comeback,
the Female Titan took out the elite members
of the Levi Squad one after another.
I'm going to kill her!
Blaming himself for trusting his comrades,
Eren made a resolute decision.
He fought in his transformed state...
...but the Female Titan
defeated him and took him away.
Give Eren...
...back!
Wherever you are,
I'm going to slaughter
this girl, butcher her body,
and get you out of that foul place...
Sorry, Eren...
Just hang on a little longer...
Wait!
Wh-What...?!
Stay back for now.
I won't let your deaths be meaningless
even if I'm the last one standing
In both hands, Gloria
What sings is Sieg
On my back, Flügel der Freiheit
Clenched determination to my left chest
What slashes across is Linie der Torheit
Soaring across the azure skies
Flügel der Freiheit
"The Defeated"
"The 57th Exterior Scouting Mission, Part 6"
Maintain this distance.
She must be worn out, too.
She's not so fast anymore.
It looked like she
bit the entire nape off.
Is Eren dead?
He's alive.
The target seems intelligent
and intent on taking Eren away.
It'd crush him if it wanted to kill him.
Instead, it's fighting and running
away with him in its mouth.
Eating Eren could be her goal.
If so, he's in her stomach.
Which means he's probably dead.
He's alive.
Let's hope so.
This never would've
happened in the first place
had you actually protected Eren!
Ah. You're that one who...
You're Eren's childhood friend.
Let's narrow our
goals down to one.
First, forget about taking her down.
She's killed so many of our comrades!
It's impossible. She has
the ability to harden her skin.
Do as I say.
We're going to set all
our hopes on Eren being alive
and rescue him before
she leaves the forest.
I'll do the cutting.
You distract her.
He's fast!
She can't even
harden her skin in time!
Her nape...
It's wide open!
She's worn-down!
I doubt she can move now!
I can kill her!
Stop!
Eren!
Hey!
Time to go!
Eren!
He seems fine.
He's filthy, but alive.
Forget about her now.
We need to withdraw.
Don't lose sight of
what this operation is about.
Is wallowing in self-indulgence
more important?
He's a dear friend to you, isn't he?
No... I'm...
They're coming back already?
What happened?
Dunno.
But I bet they'll be bringing back
another load of corpses with 'em.
It sounds like Eld is on his way back.
Oh...
Think ol' Oruo will have
time to stop by home?
I'll set a plate for him just in case!
Gunther is coming back, you know.
I see...
This is the one thing
I'll never get used to...
I doubt anyone could.
How my comrades are gonna die...
How I'm gonna die...
That's all I start to think about...
I try not to think about it at all.
Because if I started
picturing my own death,
I'd probably lose the ability to fight...
Yeah.
You're exactly right.
How long do you
think we can survive?
We've managed
to survive so far, at least.
Yeah, so far.
We should be glad. We're still alive.
Can you say that to the
bodies of the guys who died?
We might never get to
see our hometowns again.
We're nearly finished, Sir.
Five bodies or so
were unrecoverable, however.
Not even pieces of them?
The Titans didn't
leave much to recover.
I feel it'd be better for the families
if we didn't bring back what's left.
Put them down as "missing."
Yes, Sir.
We've spotted several
Titans in the vicinity of the forest,
but none are yet headed this way.
We move at once. Inform the squads.
Yes, Sir!
I refuse to accept this, Commander Erwin!
H-Hey, you!
We should recover them!
Ivan's body was
right there in front of us!
There were Titans there too!
We could end up
as casualties ourselves!
Then we can just
take 'em out if they attack!
Ivan and I grew up in the same town!
I know his parents, too!
I'd at least like to take him home!
Quit being selfish!
A bunch of brats arguing...
Captain Levi!
If you've confirmed his death,
then that's enough.
He's dead. Whether or not we
have his body makes no difference.
You can't be serious...
Ivan and the others
will be put down as "missing."
That decision is final. Just let it go.
D-Do neither of you...
...have any human feelings at all?!
Hey, Dieter! Watch what you're saying!
Titans!
That's...
...Dieter!
That idiot!
Titan spotted by the rear!
Full speed!
I don't see any large trees or buildings.
We can't fight freely out here.
Fleeing to the wall will be quicker.
It's about to catch up to us!
We're gonna have to fight!
ODM can't accomplish much on flat ground.
Plus, look.
They just keep coming!
Then what do you suggest we do?!
We need to...
It's no use! It's catching up!
I'll get behind it and distract it!
--Use that chance--
--Don't bother.
Dump the bodies. Before it catches up.
B-But, Sir...!
There've been countless people
before whose bodies were left behind.
These ones aren't somehow special.
Are we going to do it?!
Are we really going to do it?!
Damn...
We got no other choice!
That's it!
Keep moving!
We leave as soon as
we've confirmed our positions!
Stay sharp!
We need to make a slight
course correction to the east.
Captain Levi...
I...
This is proof that they once lived.
That's how I see it, anyway.
It's Ivan's.
Captain...
Let's move out!
Eren. I'd forget about the
Scout Regiment if I were you.
What?! You think the
Scout Regiment is a joke too?!
It's not about what I think.
The Scout Regiment is back!
They're gonna open the front gate!
Let's go see the heroes return, Mikasa!
Oh...!
They're the only ones who made it back?
Everyone else must've gotten eaten.
This is what they get
for going outside the walls.
Our taxes are basically going to feeding
and fattening those things up now.
Eren.
What's wrong?
Eren...
Eren!
Eren?
You shouldn't get up yet.
You need to rest.
Where's the Female Titan?!
She got away.
Why?
Why did everyone...?
What about the operation?
It failed.
You need to rest for now.
How did I get this?
Did you save me again?
We're almost to the wall now.
Is it me, or are there
fewer than this morning?
A lot fewer.
Another bad one...
They left this morning shouting and
roaring, and now they're already back?
What did they even leave for?
Beats me.
But from the brooding
looks on their faces...
...I'd say they succeeded in
pouring our tax money down the drain.
Eren. Endure it.
So cool!
The Scout Regiment's awesome!
Even when they're so
beat-up they keep on fighting!
Captain Levi, Sir!
Thanks for looking after my daughter!
I'm Petra's father!
I'd like to discuss something
before she spots me...
She sent me a letter, you see...
She said she was assigned to serve
you because you recognized her skill.
She said she wants to devote her all to you...
Basically, the girl's so starry-eyed
that she has no idea how worried her parents are!
So, well, as her father, you see...
I feel it's a bit too early
to let her get married.
She's still young and
has so much to experience...
Commander Erwin!
Please answer us!
Were the gains from this expedition
worth the number of lives lost?!
Do you honestly believe the
soldiers died without regrets?!
The costs and casualties incurred
by this latest exterior expedition
dealt a blow heavy enough to
destroy the Scout Regiment's support.
Erwin and the others in charge found
themselves summoned to the capital
and ordered to hand over Eren.
If, by chance, I'm not me
then who's to say that you're you?
Can you pick up the pieces of your heart
that fell apart like a broken sand castle?
The voice of someone calling out
changed into ringing in my ears
It's as if time has stopped
Now wake up
I made my way out of the deep darkness
I fled like a swift wind
We used to be like living corpses,
but now we head beyond the walls
Let's meet again
in a place not on any map
Annie is assigned to
the security escort team
the day Eren and the others
are summoned to the royal capital.
From out of nowhere, Armin appears
and asks for her help
in a top-secret operation.
"Smile"
"Assault on Stohess, Part 1"